Guide to the John A. Wilkinson, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
John A. Wilkinson, secretary of Yale University, records
1931-1987
RU 68
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
64.25
(120 boxes, 2 folio)
The records consist of memoranda, minutes, agendas, correspondence, speeches, organizational charts, reports, log books, and general administrative records concerning Yale's buildings and grounds, committees, departments, programs, residential colleges, policies, ethical concerns, and financial matters during John A. Wilkinson's tenure as secretary.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of memoranda, minutes, agendas, correspondence, speeches, organizational charts, reports, log books, and general administrative records concerning Yale's buildings and grounds, committees, departments, programs, residential colleges, policies, ethical concerns, and financial matters during John A. Wilkinson's tenure as secretary.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Wilkinson, John Arthur, 1938-; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale Corporation; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Administrative records of John Wilkinson and Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1967-1983; Accession 1985-A-012
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - A General, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Accession and Deaccession, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accreditation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acting Secretary, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Afro-American Encyclopedia, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alcohol, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Alumni Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alumni in New Haven Businesses, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Lists, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Magazine/Survey, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Records, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Solicitation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - American Assoc. of Universfty Profs., 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Angell, Mrs. James Rowland (Katherine), 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Applied Biology Advisory Comm., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Architecture, School of, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Art Gallery, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Associate Treasurer's Office, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Athletics
    - General, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Crew, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Football, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Harvard Game, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Medicine, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - NCM, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Tennis, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Track, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - AYA
    - California Trip, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - General (Association of Yale Alumni), 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 40 - 42)
    - Search Committee, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - B General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 44 - 46)
  - Band, Yale, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee
    - Art, Architecture and Drama: additional space, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Facilities Plan, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Facilities Plan, minutes, agenda, memoranda, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 50 - 51)
    - Minutes, agenda, memoranda, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 52 - 55)
    - School of Music: relocation and related moves, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Battel Chapel, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Beinecke Library, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Berkeley College, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Berkeley Oval Gates, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Biological Safety Advisory Comm., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Biological Science Advisory Comm., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Blohards, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Blum Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Bowl, Yale, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Branford College, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - British Art Center, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - BSAY, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Budget Office, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Budget Comm., University, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Community Relations -- General, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Community Affairs and Courtesy, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Community Relations -- Day Care, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Community Labor Alliance, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Community Relations
    - Legislation, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Parking Fees, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Personnel, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Revenue Committee, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - YMCA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - CCIC (Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges), 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 82 - 83)
  - CCIC-BHE (Board of Higher Education), 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - C General, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 85 - 87)
  - Calendar Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Calhoun College, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Campus Mail, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Canadian Studies, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Career Advisory and Placement, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Carillon Committee -- Yale, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Center Churches 84 Trumbull St., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Chaplain Vannorsdall, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Charities Drive, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Chauncey, Henry Jr., 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Chemistry, Lab, Sterling, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Class of 1960, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Class Scheduling, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Cognitive, Science, Ad Hoc Committee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Collaborative Research Policy Statement, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Collar, President"s, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Commencement
    - Baccalaureate '82, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Baccalaureate '81, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Communications, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Computer Center, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Consilium-International and Area Studies, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Connecticut, University of, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - CT Agricultural Experiment Station, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - CT Hall Plate, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Cooperative Research Director, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Council, Yale College, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Council of Masters '81-'82, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Council of Masters '80-'81, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Council of Masters '79-'80, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Custodial Services, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - D General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Daily News, Yale, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Data Systems, University, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Davenport College, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Deans Groups, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Dean's Portraits, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Department Chairmen, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - DeVane Lectures, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Development Campaign for Yale, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Development -- General, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 133 - 136)
  - Development Office Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Development "Shopping List", 1982 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Development Office -- V-P for Development, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Dining Halls, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Directory, University, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Divinity School, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Divinity School Dean's Installation, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Dramat School, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Dues, Professional Organizations, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Dwight, Timothy, College, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Dwight Hall, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - E General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Eleven O'clock Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Eli International, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Energy, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Engineering, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Entrance to Student Rooms, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Equal Opportunity Statement, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - ETS (Educational Testing.Service), 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Expository Writing, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Ezra Stiles -- Monument Rededication, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - F General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Faculty Appointments, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Faculty
    - Disciplinary Procedures, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Emeritus, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Handbook, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 169)
    - Legal Fees Payment, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Faculty Retirees, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Retirement Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Salaries, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Welcoming Letter, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Yale Degrees, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Finance and Administration Office, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Financial Aid, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Financial Counseling Program, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Financial Reporting Systems Comm., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Fire, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Florists, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Foreign Governments' Contracts and Gifts, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Foreign Students Office, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Forestry School, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Forest Search -- 1981 (Box 12, Folder 190 - 193)
  - Four-Hundred List Mailings, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Freshman Assemblies, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Friends of Am. Art at Yale, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - G General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - Gays/Lesbians, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - General Counsel Office, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 201 - 202)
  - General Counsel-Acting, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 203)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 204)
  - ABG Athletic Speech 1980 (Box 13, Folder 205)
  - Glee Club, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 206)
  - Graduate and Professional Assemblies, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 207)
  - Graduate Club Association, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 208)
  - Graduate School, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 209)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney: Speeches, Articles and Reports, 1951-1962 (Box 13, Folder 211)
  - Griswold, Mary Brooks, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 212)
  - Grove Street Cemetary, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 213)
  - Gym, 1980-1991 (Box 13, Folder 214)
  - H General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 215)
  - Hale, Statue of Nathan, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 216)
  - Halloween, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 217)
  - Hand Gun Control, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 219)
  - Handicapped Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 220)
  - Harassment Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 13a, Folder 221)
  - Harassment -- Sexual, 1979-1980 (Box 13a, Folder 222)
  - Harden Furniture, 1981 (Box 13a, Folder 223)
  - Harvard University, 1980-1981 (Box 13a, Folder 224)
  - Havemeyer, 1982 (Box 13a, Folder 225)
  - Health Center, 1980 (Box 13a, Folder 226)
  - Hill Day Care Center, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 228)
  - Hillhouse Ave. #31, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 229)
  - Hillhouse Ave. #43, 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 230)
  - Hillhouse Avenue -- General, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 231)
  - Historic Preservation, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 232)
  - Historical Commission, Connecticut, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 233)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 237)
  - Housing -- Undergraduate, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 239)
  - Human Relations Counselors, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 240)
  - I General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 241)
  - I.D. Cards, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 242)
  - Information Office, Yale, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 243)
  - Intern Program, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 244)
  - International Center, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 245)
  - I.S.P.S. (Institution for Social and Policy Studies), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 246)
  - J General Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 247)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 249)
  - Judaic Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 250 - 251)
  - K General Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 252)
  - Keys, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 255)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 257)
  - L General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 258)
  - Lang, Serge, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 259)
  - LaRouche Visit, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 260)
  - Law School, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 261)
  - Lectureships, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 262)
  - Lee, R.C., 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 263)
  - Leeney Dinner, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 264)
  - Legislation, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 265)
  - Liasion Program, Yale, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 268)
  - Library Disciplinary Regulations, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 269)
  - Library, Sterling, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 270)
  - Loan Forms (HEW), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 272)
  - Mac and Mc General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 277)
  - M General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 279)
  - Mail Log -- 1981 Jun - Dec (Box 17, Folder 280)
  - Management Intern Program, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 281)
  - Managerial and Professional Comm., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 282)
  - Maps, Colored, undated (Box 17, Folder 283)
  - Medal, Yale, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 286)
  - Media Design Studio (Herbert Brodkin Film -- Jul 27, 2:00), 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 287)
  - Medicine, School of, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 288)
  - Memorial Services, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 289)
  - Mini-Bus, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 290)
  - Minority Advisory Council, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 291 - 292)
  - Minority-Black - Grad. Network, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 293)
  - Minority Meetings, 1977-1981 (Box 18, Folder 294 - 295)
  - Minority Student Coordinators, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 296)
  - Minority Students Internships, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 297)
  - Morse College Mastership, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 298)
  - Moving Expenses, Administrators, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 299)
  - Mr. Coffee, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 300)
  - Music School, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 301)
  - N General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 302)
  - Natural Preserve, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 303)
  - Natural Preserve Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 304)
  - N.H. Colony Historical Society, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 305)
  - New York City Yale Club, 1970-1975 (Box 19, Folder 307)
  - New York Giants, undated (Box 19, Folder 308)
  - Nondiscrimination Statement, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 309)
  - North Haven Mall, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 310)
  - Nursing School, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 311)
  - O General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 312)
  - Objectives and Staff Review-1980 (Box 19, Folder 313)
  - Officers Emergency Procedures, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 314)
  - Office Procedures Committee, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 315)
  - Officers, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 316)
  - Officers Insurance, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 317)
  - Old Campus Furniture, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 318)
  - Olin, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 319)
  - Organizational Charts, undated (Box 19, Folder 320)
  - Organization and Management, School of, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 321)
  - P General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 322)
  - Parking and Communications, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 323)
  - Peabody Museum, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 324)
  - Personnel Office, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 325)
  - Personnel Records Inspection, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 326)
  - Petard, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 327)
  - Pets, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 328)
  - Physical Plant, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 329)
  - Physics Department, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 330)
  - Pierson, George -- Yale History Office, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 331)
  - Pierson College, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 332)
  - Planning Sessions, Summer 1980 (Box 20, Folder 333)
  - Political Union, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 334)
  - President's Office, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 335)
  - Press Board of Governors, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 336)
  - Princeton University, 1976-1981 (Box 20, Folder 337)
  - Printing Service, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 338)
  - Priorities and Planning Council, 1977-1982 (Box 20, Folder 339)
  - Prizes, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 340)
  - Proctor and Gamble, undated (Box 21, Folder 341)
  - Protection of Human Subjects, undated (Box 21, Folder 342)
  - Provost's Office, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 344)
  - Psychology Department, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 345)
  - Q General Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 346)
  - Quinnipiac College Nominating Comm., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 347)
  - R General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 348)
  - Race Relations Committee, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 349)
  - Racial Insensitivity, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 350)
  - Racism Discussion Group, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 351)
  - Recommendations, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 354)
  - Research Development Committee, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 355 - 356)
  - Residences Committee
    - 87 Trumbull St. (87 Trumbull-Wilkinson), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 357)
    - Inventories, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 358)
    - 31 Hillhouse Ave., 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 359)
  - Retirement, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 360)
  - Reunions, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 361)
  - Review Committee -- Non-Academic Administrative, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 362 - 366)
  - R.O.T.C., 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 369)
  - Russian Chorus, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 370)
  - S General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 371 - 373)
  - Sacred Music Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 375)
  - Salute to New Haven, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 376)
  - Science Park, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 377 - 379)
  - Sculpture Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 380)
  - Sculpture Maintenance -- Outdoor (Smalley, Jed), 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 381)
  - Search Committees, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 382)
  - Search Procedures -- Administrative, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 383)
  - Secretaries -- Ivy, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 384)
  - Secretary's Office, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 385)
  - Seeley-Mudd Cornerstone, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 386)
  - Senior Societies, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 387)
  - Sheraton Park Plaza Survey, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 389)
  - Shuttle Bus Information, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 390)
  - Sign Project, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 391 - 392)
  - Silliman, Benjamin -- 200th Birthday, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 393)
  - Silliman College, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 394)
  - Silver, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 395)
  - Skillman Associates, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 397)
  - Snetco, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 398)
  - Social Sciences Research Report, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 399)
  - Solotke Memorial, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 400)
  - South Africa -- Ethical Investments, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 401)
  - South Central Community College, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 402)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conf., 1979 (Box 25, Folder 403)
  - Southern Connecticut State College, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 404)
  - "Staff Reporter", 1980 (Box 25, Folder 405)
  - Stained Glass at Yale, 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 406)
  - Statistics -- Faculty and Students, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 407)
  - Sterling Chemistry Lab, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 408)
  - Student Agencies, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 412)
  - Student Furnishings, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 413)
  - Student Patrols, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 414)
  - Summer/Special Programs, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 415 - 416)
  - Sympathy Letters, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 417)
  - T General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 418)
  - Teachers Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 419)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 420)
  - Terry Lectures, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 421)
  - Toad's Place, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 423)
  - Tours of Campus, Guided, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 425)
  - Travel Offices, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 426)
  - Tribunal, University, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 427)
  - Trumbull College, 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 429)
  - Turnbull Lunch, 1981 January 21 (Box 27, Folder 430)
  - U General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 431)
  - Union, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 432)
  - United Way, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 434)
  - University Council-General, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 435 - 436)
  - University Operations, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 437)
  - V General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 438)
  - Van Sinderen Book Collecting Competition, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 439)
  - W General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 441)
  - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 442)
  - WELI, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 443)
  - Wells Fellowship, The Damon, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 444)
  - Whitney Humanities Center, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 448)
  - Widows, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 449)
  - Wiggin and Dana, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 450)
  - Wilderness School, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 451)
  - Women -- General, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 453)
  - Woodbridge Hall, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 454)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 455)
  - Word Processing Committee, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 456)
  - WYBC, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 457)
  - X,Y,Z General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 458)
  - Yale Arms, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 459)
  - Yale Banner Publications, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 460)
  - Yale Charter, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 461)
  - Yale-China Association, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 462)
  - Yale Collection, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 463)
  - Yale College Calendar, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 464)
  - Yale College Dean's Office, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 465)
  - Yale Co-Operative Corp., 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 466)
  - Yale Facilities, Use of, for filming, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 467)
  - Yale Fence, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 468)
  - Yale Lit. Folder #2, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 469)
  - Yale Name -- Protection of, 1978-1982 (Box 29, Folder 470 - 471)
  - Yale Name Task Force, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 472)
  - Yale Quarterly, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 473)
  - Yale Science and Engineering Assoc., 1978-1982 (Box 29, Folder 474)
  - Yale Seal, Use of, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 475)
  - Yale Station, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 476)
  - Telephone Log Books
    - 1980 Nov 24 - 1981 Oct 1 (Box 30, Folder 477 - 481)
    - 1981 Oct 1 - 1982 Jul 26 (Box 31, Folder 482 - 485)
  - Secretary Henry Chauncey
    - A-Z: general file, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 486)
    - Bursary Aids, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 490)
    - Development, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 492)
    - Loans, Students, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 495)
    - Security: 43 Hillhouse Avenue, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 496)
- Records, 1976-1984; Accession 1987-A-047
  - Administrative Files, 1976-1984
    - A -- General correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
    - Admissions
      - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Undergraduate (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Alcohol (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Alterations Revlew Committee (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Angell, Mrs. James Roland (Katherine) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Athletics
      - Golf (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Harvard Game (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - AYA -- General (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - AYA Trips -- General (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - B -- General Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 18 - 19)
    - Band, Yale (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Berkeley College (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Branford College (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - B and G Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 24 - 26)